Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Itfriend.VN www.Addic7ed.com
We're back. Okay...
Here's another question
we got at iCarly. Com...
Which says...
"Last night, I dreamt
"that Gibby could fly.
"Would you guys please make
my dream come true?"
Yes.
- Ready Gibbles?
- Call it.
Fly!!!
Weee!!
I'm a bird!
Ha, ha.
- Oh my God!
- I'm flying!!
Look at him fly!
Gibby's flying!
Ha, ha. Whoa.
Wee!! Ha, ha.
I'm a...
Gibbeh...
Uhhh...
Now Freddie's gonna say something.
Hey there.
Let's chat while Carly and Sam
safely drag Gibby away.
So...How ya been?
I like baseball.
You tell your mother you tripped
and fell down the stairs.
Understood.
Okay.
- We're back!
- Gibby's fine.
Not really!
And that's it for iCarly tonight.
- That is not it.
- Gib, c'mon...
What is this, another intervention?
- Noooo...
- Nuh-uh...
We're here to congratulate
my best friend, Sam...
Because she hasn't gotten
into any kind of trouble...
- Zero trouble...
- For 10 whole days.
It's true!
And it's the first time that's
happened since I was four.
Well, we invited a very special
guest to come here today.
And give you a very special reward.
Who?!
The mayor of Seattle!
Mayor Mustachio!
Ha, ha, ha.
Greetings ye citizens!
Samantha Puckett, as fake mayor of Seattle,
I shall grab my lapel
as I hereby, henceforth,
hither to and fro...
Yeah, yeah, what do I get?
Sam, for going 10 full days
without getting into any trouble,
I present to you...
This box of raisins...
- Okaaay.
- This bag, I got from a dog Walker.
Ooo, still warm.
And this movie,
directed by David Schwimmer...
Also still warm.
And this.
What's the...
No way, shut up!
We shall not shut up.
- Tell the fans whatcha got.
- Yes.
Sam Puckett, this ticket
is good for a V.I.P. Tour.
Of the canadian fat cake factory!
Canadian fat cakes
aren't even allowed in America.
And I've heard they're like way
better than American fat cakes!
What do you have to say
about all this, Mayor Mustachio?
I say...
My mayor trousers are too tight
in the crotch!
- That's charming.
- I didn't need to know that.
- Yeah, brilliant.
- Whoa, oh, okay.
Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Itfriend.VN www.Addic7ed.com
In 5, 4, 3, 2...
I know, you see
somehow the world will change for me
and be so wonderful
live life, breathe air
I know somehow we're gonna get there
and feel so wonderful
it's all for real
I'm tellin' you just how I feel
so wake up the members of my nation
it's your time to be
there's no chance unless you take one
and a time to see
the brighter side of every situation
some things are meant to be
so give it your best
and leave the rest to me
leave it all to me
just leave it all to me
Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Itfriend.VN www.Addic7ed.com
Why are you bringing a big suitcase?
We're just going to Canada for the day.
Yeah... so I brought
some hair care products,
some extra batteries,
a change of underpants...
Is that a problem?
No.
That's what I thought.
C'mon guys.
We gotta hit the road.
We don't have to be at the
fat cake factory 'til one.
- Yeah,
but it's a two-hour drive,
we gotta go through security at the border.
Why?
It's not like Canada's a different country.
Yes, it is.
I thought it was like Idaho.
Idaho is a state...
In our country.
Look, I don't need a lecture.
You sure you're not gonna come?
I want to but I already bailed on
Lance twice and he's really cool.
And if I bail again, he's
gonna think I don't like him,
and I really do like him.
Besides, I haven't kissed a guy in
four months, I'm gettin' itchy.
What time's your date?
Handsome Lance is picking
me up at five o'clock.
With his car.
So what are you gonna do 'til then?
Probably take a long hot bath,
and I'll blow my hair out,
maybe I'll do my nails...
- Bye.
- Late.
- See ya.
- Gibbehh.
-...This dirtbag,
call our toll-free hotline...
Nah.
Next on the dingo channel!
She sings! He dances!
And they're both identical twin ninjas!
So stay tuned for twinjas!
You think I purposely got
the peruvian puff peppers,
knowing you'd steal them from me
and use them in your own salsa?
Seen it.
- I got stuck my foot in.
- Now, what on...
Yay, the Vintage network.
- Let me have the foot.
- It's stuck!
- How's that one?
- C'mon.
A lady can't get her big toe
stuck in a faucet.
- What for?
- Tell me...
Is that toe similar to the one
that's stuck in the pipe?
Well, of course it is!
Why?
Wouldn't want to nip off
any of this little piggie.
Man...
Sitcoms are so much better now.
In...
Out.
Duh.
In...
Out.
No...
Noooo...
Stupid overly realistic sitcoms.
Okay, okay...
Just gotta stay calm...
Got tons of time before Lance gets here...
Just gotta be calm, sooner or
later, someone'll come in here,
help me get my toe unstuck and...
...And see me naked!!!
Uhhh...
My sweatshirt!
Here in Canada, we produce over 65
per cent of the world's fat cakes.
Thank you, Canada!
Now... this is one of our central
fat cake production areas.
In just this room alone, over ninety-five
thousand fat cakes are injected with cream.
And sent through for packaging every day.
- What do you think of that?
- I think they're beautiful.
M... mm... momma's home.
Awww.
She really likes fat cakes.
Yes.
You all are from America, right?
- U.S.A.
- estados unidos.
Gibbehh.
Well have you ever tried
a canadian fat cake?
- N-no sir.
'Cuz our intrusive federal
government made 'em illegal.
Are canadian fat cakes
as magical as people say?
- Magicaler.
- What makes 'em so amazing?
They're made with pure cane fat.
Right.
In America we use corn fat.
I'm the tour guide!
I say the words!
Sorry.
- Wow, angry canadian.
- You don't see that very often.
Now... which of you Americans
would like to be the first.
To try a canadian fat cake?
Hey, I wouldn't mind bein'...
May I?
- Okay, Sam... take a bite...
- Shut up!!!
I need to focus.
Oh...
Ohhh...
Ohhhhh...
It's really good, huh?
It's so much better than good.
It's like eating a fat angel.
Okay...
I just gotta get my pear phone...
And then... I can call for help.
I'm comin' for you, phone.
I do throw like a girl.
Okay, put a little more sauce
on this one...
I'll put a little less sauce on this one.
Okay.
Are you Americans ready
to inject some fat cakes?
- Oh yes.
- Yes.
So what's in these bags?
We call them "fat bags."
Each one contains two kilos
of our creamy filling.
Now, you just insert the nozzle...
- Insert the nozzle!
- Into the fat cake...
- Into the fat cake!
- And then squeeeeeeze the sack until the fat cake...
I'm gonna need another fat bag.
All right c'mon!
I've hit everything else.
Yes! Yes!
Good throw, me.
And nowwww...
There it is!
Now, come to Carly...
Easy...
Eeeeaaasssyyyy...
Remember how cute Lance is...
Aaaaannnd... gotcha!
Woooooo!!! Okay.
Now I just call Wendy
and tell her to come over and...
Well, there's no app for that.
C'mon, let's just drive
across the border and go home.
We can't.
It's illegal to cross the border without
letting these people check our stuff,
- and our passports...
- Blehh blehh blehh blehhhh.
I know you have a crush on me.
- What?
- Nothin'.
So if Idaho wanted to be
its own country... could it?
I guess they could try...
But it'd probably start another civil war.
War? War is wack.
Well said, my friend.
- Canadian fat cake?
- Gibby...You gotta get rid of that.
- Is that a canadian fat cake?
- Yeah, I got a few of 'em.
Dude, you can't bring those
across the border into America.
- They're illegal in the U.S.
- okay!
- Now throw 'em away!
- Before you make these border cops suspicious!
I get it!
- Come on.
- You guys, come get in line.
Whoa... large dog.
Whoa.
Okay, good dog, go on now...
Nothing to smell here...
Miss, are you crossing
the border into America?
Uhhh...
'Scuze me... is there a
problem with these kids...
Who may or may not be with me?
Are you crossing the border into America?
Yeah, I'm about to.
Go on now, puppy... shoo...
He probably just smells my dog on me.
- You don't have a dog.
- I will hurt you with a brick.
- Check her coat.
- What? No, no, no, no.
No need to check my coat.
I appreciate your concern.
That's...
Fat cakes.
Whaaaaaaaat?! Let go of me...
Spencer!
W
Okay.
That's all the fat cakes she had on her.
Look at that.
That's gotta be
twenty-five kilos.
What did you plan to do
with all these fat cakes?
Well, mustache,
I was gonna put 'em in my face,
chew 'em a little, send 'em on
a trip down to my stomach...
And I think we all know what would
happened to 'em after that.
And now a sip for you.
- Dogs really like you.
- Yeah.
Dogs and girls
with low self-esteem.
Are you miss Puckett's guardian?
Uh, well...
Actually, I'm her Attorney.
Y'know... lawyer?
- You're a lawyer?
- Are you gonna check?
- No.
- Yeah I'm a lawyer.
And I demand to know
why my client is being detained.
Because she attempted to smuggle
over a hundred canadian fat cakes.
Across the border into the United States.
Which is illegal.
Oh.
And she called me a dumb wazz bag.
- I object!
- So did I.
I don't even know what a wazz bag is.
Well... if you had a bag...
And you, you know,
needed to wazz, then it'd be...
He doesn't need to know.
C'mon, please let me go home.
I'm just a sweet little girl who
got caught up with a bad crowd.
How'd you get those handcuffs off?
Just a trick I learned in juvie.
I demand that miss Puckett
be released on the grounds.
That... section c...
If you'll shut up, we will release her.
But I... say what?
- You're really gonna let me go?!
- That's right.
So basically you hassled me for nothing?
See, this is the kind of chiz that...
Uhhh, my client accepts your terms
and will now happily shut her face.
- No, they harassed me over-
- shut... her... f'hace.
Just go over there, show your ids, and
you can all enter the United States.
Gibbehh...
- That's you?
- Yeah, I know. The long hair was a bad call.
"Fredward". Go ahead.
You're on iCarly, right?
You know, I also write a blog
about card tricks.
- Gibby, come on.
- How come no one asks about my blog?!
- Passport?
- I don't have a passport.
- Do you have a driver's license?
- A real one?
- Yes.
- No.
- School id?
- Threw it at a bird.
- Library card?
- Who is this guy?
Library card.
- You can't re-enter America unless
you can prove you're a U.S. citizen.
Dude, I promise she is.
Can't you just ask her some
question so she can prove it?
Fine.
Who was the first
U.S. president?
The father of our country?
Abraham Franklin?
That's not it?
Heelllpppp! Heelllpppp!
I have a cute date
in less than thirty minutes!
Heelllpppp!! Helfen-meer!
Helfen-meer!!
...Nah, I'm just ironing
Freddie's underwear.
No... we're not renting
bowling shoes.
Because I refuse to put my feet
in public footwear.
Oh, that spray doesn't do anyth...
Wait...
I hear something peculiar.
Heellpp!!! Heelllpppp!
Heellpp!! Hellpp!! Ossy-stonce!
Anyone! Pleeeaaase!
A cute boy is gonna be here any minute.
And I'm all wrinkled
like an elderly raisin!
Awww!
This day could not get worse!!!
- Ulch, it's you.
- Mrs. Benson!
Will you stop banging and screaming?!
I heard you all the way in my apartment!
- That was the point!!!
- Oh. You bathe in your sweatshirt too?
I thought I was the only one.
I don't bathe in a sweatshirt!
I got my toe stuck in the faucet!
- How? - I saw some dumb person
do it on the Dick van dyke show.
Come on, could you please
just help me get it out?
All right, I'll give it a yank.
Ready?
Okay, just be really careful, okay?
- Ahhhh!
- Owwwwww!
- Am I hurting you?
- No, I love it!
- Hey, is everything all right?
- Lance!
Sorry... I heard screaming
so I thought I should come up.
Put your hands down!
Who's the boy?
My date.
Hey.
Heyyyy.
- Oh, man, this is bad.
- Yeah, for you.
- Me?
- You're the adult!
You're the one who brought Sam to Canada.
And now can't get her back home!
I know!
I'd be in serious trouble
if she had a parent who cared.
True.
But still, we gotta figure...
Okay, let's get across
that border and head home.
- Dude...
- We're not just gonna leave Sam in Canada.
Shhhh!
We're not gonna leave her.
- Are we across the border yet?
- Not yet.
Well hurry!
- Okay, let's go.
- Oh my gosh, it's Gibby!
Can I have your autograph?!
Please please please?
Uhhhh... here it goes again.
Hurry, just do it!
Yes!
Uh... you know
I'm part of iCarly, too.
You are?
Yeah, I work the camera, do the...
Ooo, awesome!
Here, take a pic of me with Gibby!
Hold this please. Gibbeh!!
I don't take my shirt off anymore.
You should! Kids love it!
All right, in five four three two click.
- Gibby?
- Okay, let's get outta here.
- Grab Sam, let's go.
- Ooo. Sam's light.
- Come on!
- U-S-A! U-S-A! U-S-A! U-S-A!
- Come on. Really?
- It's true.
Your sister's eighteen and she
doesn't have her driver's license?
- Nope.
- That's so sad!
Yeah, she's lame.
- But you know who's not lame?
- Who?
- You.
- Awww. You're not lame too.
Well, if you two are gonna kiss, go on and
do it before I fire up this power saw.
Aw, that's nice.
Just yell if I hit bone!
Thank you for flying air Malaysia.
We will be landing shortly.
Freddie?! Spencer?! Gibby?!
Are we still in Canada?!
Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Itfriend.VN www.Addic7ed.com
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0